you would take out the body, whether
it's a a body double or, you know, made
out of silicone or whatever. Take it out
in full view of everybody.
That's how I would do it.
Let as many people as possible see this
body.
So that reasonable people
can agree to disagree.
>> They did do that.
>> Mhm.
>> Hello, I'm John Kiriakou and I'm here to
[__] [__] up.
>> [music]
>> You're like the most famous guy on the
internet now. I don't recognize your
normal voice. It's killing me.
>> I know, right?
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know how this happened.
It just happened like literally
overnight. It just happened.
>> [laughter]
>> Can we pull up the latest one that we
put up, Steve?
>> Yeah.
>> Let's get John's live reaction. So, when
this was happening, when you and I did
episodes 278 and 279 together, which was
a year ago,
I remember this was probably like an
hour 20 something minutes into the first
episode and I remember this whole
Lincoln thing coming up out of nowhere.
I'm like, "God, this is cool. He's a
Lincoln collector." And then you look at
me with a dead straight face and you're
like, "Yeah, I was trying to buy
Lincoln's last turd." And I at the time
we had Alessia in the studio and I'm I'm
I'm like turning to Alessia like this,
"This [__]
And then you're like, "Oh yeah, I was
trying to buy it." So, when this all
started to break like Danny on on our
editing team and and I were we're
looking at stuff. I'm like, "You got to
make the Lincoln [__] story." [laughter]
So, he he did. Let's run it.
Can people see this, Steve?
>> Yeah.
>> All right, let's roll.
>> show museum
>> It was a museum of circus freak shows
from the 1800s. The stuff that had been
in these circus side shows. They had the
shadow box hanging on the wall. And
there's
>> dried out turd [clears throat]
>> And it says it is
>> Abraham Lincoln's final turd.
>> Come on. So, it says on the card, it
said when he arrived at Ford's Theater,
he had to drop a deuce. And so, before
he got seated, he went to the men's
room.
>> And he dropped a deuce in the chamber
pot.
>> And then he went back to watch the play.
>> And he got shot.
>> And somebody had the presence of mind
>> to [__] out of
>> And they say presence of mind
>> over the sickness.
>> Well,
>> a gorilla of Lincoln collecting
>> [laughter]
>> I see her to go and watch the post about
6 months later saying he's going out of
business and they're going to auction
everything off. So, I told my wife,
>> I'm buying that turd.
>> She's like,
>> Oh, no, you're not.
>> I said,
>> Oh, yes, I am. I'm buying that turd.
>> My wife and I actually had a strong
disagreement about this. We go to the
auction and I
>> I top out at 1,200 bucks.
>> And it ends up going to 5 grand. So, the
guy that ended up buying it sends it to
some company for a DNA sample. And what
they found was it had like microscopic
bits of a Necco Wafer in it, but Necco
Wafers weren't invented until 1880.
>> It wasn't his [__] It wasn't his.
>> [laughter]
>> It was some random guy's turd.
>> And that's what he paid for.
>> He paid
$5,000 for.
>> [laughter]
>> That is one of my better stories.
>> Oh my god. Are you familiar with Black
Twitter at all?
>> No.
>> Oh, you're not. You You need to
familiarize yourself. They love you.
>> You really?
>> They love Yotes this [__] John.
Crazy, yo.
>> [laughter]
>> There's my I some words I'm not allowed
to say. This [__] I hear just
saying straight cap, but it's real.
[laughter]
And I'm I'm [__] dying reading this
stuff.
>> And I'm telling you it happened
literally overnight.
>> Yeah.
>> And I don't understand why.
>> I know you don't. I mean, you're like
for people that don't know you
personally, which is pretty much
everyone out there listening, like
you've lived this amazing life and done
all all these incredible things or
whatever, but it's always funny to talk
to you like about content cuz you're
like, "Oh, is that good?"
>> [laughter]
>> I'm like, "Yeah, John, like 15 million
views on something's really good." And
you're like, "Okay." And you leave.
[laughter]
And we're just like, "You know what?
You're happy as a clam. We'll keep it
that way."
>> And you know,
some crazy stuff has happened since I
saw you last. I've got this great friend
Tyrel Ventura, Jesse Ventura's son. Ty
is one of the sweetest men I've ever
I've ever met. He's just a really
good-hearted, kind guy.
>> What's up, guys? Three quick things.
Number one, if you have not already
subscribed, please hit that subscribe
button. It is a huge huge help. Number
two, if you'd like to join my Patreon
for early uncensored releases of these
episodes, you can join via the link in
my description or my pinned comment. And
number three, if you'd like to join my
clipping community for a chance to edit
clips from the show and make money, you
can join via the Discord link in my
description below.
>> And he calls me one night in July
and uh
and he says uh he wrote a movie. And
Ty's Ty's a Hollywood guy. He's he's
done a lot in in film. He wrote this
movie. I was like, "Oh, that's cool.
Good for you." And he said, "Well, you
know, it's going to be this is the
story." I was like, "Yeah, that actually
sounds like a compelling uh storyline."
>> [laughter]
>> And I'm thinking, "Why is he telling me
this?" I'm happy for him. He's going to
write this movie.
And he said, "Uh you're going to be in
my movie."
And I said, "Oh, thank you. No. No, no,
I'm not interested. I said, "Listen,
I'll be stiff and uh unconvincing. I'm I
would be a terrible actor. I've never
acted before and I would wreck your
movie." And he said, "Well, I thought of
that. And I thought you've been
you acted every day of your career when
you were with the CIA." I said, "Well,
that's actually that's actually true."
And he said, "So,
I wrote the part specifically for you
and you're going to be in the movie."
So, I went to Mexico for the whole month
of October.
>> Wow.
>> And we filmed this movie.
And I'm very proud to say that I am now
a member of the Screen Actors Guild.
>> Oh, you're in SAG now.
>> [laughter]
>> That's not suspicious at all. So, a CIA
guy in SAG.
>> I'm also now a professional Hollywood
actor.
>> Were you Did you feel like you were good
at it when you were doing it? I feel
like you're a natural.
>> No, I Listen, everybody around me,
everybody else in the film was
incredible. Like, I would stand there
just off camera watching them in awe of
their ability to do this over and over
and over again. Scene We would do each
scene eight, 10, 12 times.
>> Right.
>> And they were so good. And they've all
been in stuff. They've all been in
movies and TV series and all kinds of
stuff. And then the star of the movie is
a
a really great guy, very generous with
his time and his advice, Jeff Fahey. I
really hit it off with him.
He would stand just off camera and
whisper directions to me.
And it made me like, I guess,
believable enough that I didn't make an
ass of myself in this movie. So, we
watched the first cut a couple of
Saturdays ago
and I was like,
this movie's actually good.
Like, I would go to the theater to watch
it.
>> it about?
>> It's about the richest guy in the world
who's a cross between Elon Musk and um
and uh Erik Prince.
And
he has a son who has become his
daughter.
And so they're estranged. And he hasn't
told anybody, but he's dying of liver
cancer. And so he invites the the
country's
preeminent
lefty podcaster and the country's
preeminent righty podcaster to come and
he's going to tell his story for the
first time. And then they sort of are
competing with one another how they're
[snorts] going to shape the story. One
falls apart, the other one gets it done.
And then I'm the director of the guy's
security detail,
a former CIA ops officer.
>> Oh, right on cue. There you go.
But you had to play a bit of a tough
guy, right?
>> Yeah, I had to play an [__] The guy
was an [__] And and a liar.
>> You couldn't play that. I was in a
dumpster all night.
>> That's another one that's making the
rounds.
>> [laughter]
>> Do I smell like I've been with a woman?
>> And then the best is they switch it back
and your voice is like, we later got
divorced.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm going to [__] laugh. Oh my god.
Oh, I'm going to start crying.
>> Oh, well, that's very good. I'm I'm glad
you're in SAG now. You so you I just add
it to the resume, right?
>> Last night I cast my votes for the SAG
Awards. Now now call the actor awards.
>> Excellent.
>> I took it very seriously. They they They
send everybody They're like, you know,
50 million people that are in the SAG.
So
it it's not like, you know, this was
anything necessarily special. It was for
me. So they send you the list of
nominees. They send you links to every
one of the movies and the TV series. I
watched every last one of them. And I
cast educated votes.
>> Good for you, John. Someone's taking it
seriously. [laughter] They need your
type in there.
>> That's right.
>> But we we are we are here obviously as
like kind of an emergency episode
because of what's going on. And I know
you have
some stuff that you heard, whispers in
the wind if you will, about Iran. So we
will get to that a little bit later, but
I definitely want to start on the
story of my lifetime, I think is what I
would say at this point. You and I have
talked about it in the past on episodes
with Epstein and, you know, how they've
slowly rolled out this case and people
have found information over the years
and now there's some files coming out
and there's a lot of issues there. But I
got to tell you, man,
reading through these emails
>> Yeah.
>> [snorts]
>> Sickening.
>> There are so many things that in the
past people might have presented to me,
random people,
with
let's say no evidence that I was like,
come on.
>> Yeah.
>> And now Right?
>> That's been my response. Like, come on.
>> So
now when you read it, are you like me
where you're like, well, I can't rule
this out anymore?
>> I will say I've got a great friend, Ben
Swan, terrific investigative journalist,
who was laser-focused on Pizzagate. And
Pizzagate always sounded so insane to me
that I was like, come on, man. What are
you doing? You're going to kill your
career with this Pizzagate thing. The
first of all, the pizza place doesn't
even have a basement where they're
keeping kids, right? And this clown from
North Carolina drives up with an AR-15
or whatever it was, AK-47, and shoots
the place up, and then he can't find a
basement where the kids are being kept
as sex slaves and he, you know, gives
himself up.
And then we see these emails last week
about, you know, take a Viagra and then
we'll go get some pizza and grape soda.
Ha ha ha.
It's it's nuts. I can't believe it in
some of these cases.
>> And the you know, the the the code word
usage. The The other thing, John, that's
so sinister is
it's almost like it was a giant, you
know, [__] you meme to everyone. Like
the worst sadistic kind because you have
a guy emailing from account from an
account called j e e vacation. Like you
can't even make this up. That's like
what your grandpa would make on an auto
AOL account back in 1999 when he wanted
to be hip and make an email.
>> Mhm.
>> You know what I mean? And they talk so
flippantly. Like forget the most
sadistic stuff where they're talking
about children and the awful things
they're doing to them.
>> Mhm.
>> Like that, but they talk so flippantly
about the world and it had me rethinking
what George Carlin once said. I always
quote it. Everyone always quotes it.
It's a big club and you're not in it.
>> That's right.
>> I think we have to fix the quote. It's a
little club
and you're not in it.
>> We didn't even We didn't even realize
this little club existed within the big
club.
>> Mhm.
>> I think that is fair.
>> Yeah.
>> I tried a psychoactive mushroom
recently. You've heard me talk about it
before. It's not the one everyone always
talks about though. The mushroom I'm
referring to is Amanita Muscaria. Red
one with the white spots that you've
seen in folklore stories forever. It's
not psilocybin and it's not a
traditional psychedelic. Although at
high doses it can be extremely
dissociative and psychoactive in its own
way. For me, it's way more grounding. At
lower doses it puts you in a calmer,
focused, almost flow state headspace. At
medium doses it's more relaxing and
sedating, which is great for sleep and
dreams. Personally, I like Amanita at
lower doses. It makes me calmer and
relaxed and it's not this crazy like
high feeling or anything like that. The
reason I felt comfortable even trying
Amanita in the first place though is
because of Amanita Tara. This entire
space is filled with a bunch of sketchy
mushroom products and these guys are the
opposite clean sourcing no synthetics no
fillers and a huge focus on education.
So if you'd like to join me and check
out Amanita for yourself. You can go to
www.amanita.com/go/julian
that link is in my description below and
use code jd22 at checkout for 22% off
your entire order. Once again, that's
www.amanita.com/go/julian
link in my description below and don't
forget to use code jd22 for 22% off your
order. What do you think of what Tucker
said about this revealing perhaps some
sort of super government like s u p r a
where
he said the people that you thought were
the highest actually just work for the
people who work for the people that are
the highest.
>> Isn't that the truth? I think he's onto
something.
You know, Tucker's another guy who um
has been very deliberate about all this.
He was never one to jump on rumor. He
was always one of the guys who demanded
to see evidence
before he took a position.
[clears throat]
And I think even he is shocked by what
has been released. And you know, there
are a million other little strings that
haven't been pulled yet. Don't forget
there are still reportedly between 3 and
3.3 million documents that have not yet
been released.
>> Yes.
>> That Pam Bondi has said won't be
released. She's going to defy
a bill passed 419 to 1 in the house and
99 to nothing in the Senate and signed
by the president and she's just going to
say, "No,
I'm not going to do what the bill
commands me to do and release these
documents."
>> Do you think she's saying that or that's
coming from above her?
>> It has to be coming from above her. It
has to be.
One of these little strings that I've
been trying to focus on involves Kathryn
Remler who was the Obama
administration's uh
White House counsel.
>> 11,500 emails.
>> First of all, what the [__] right?
Like does she do nothing all day long as
the White House counsel other than
chit-chat with Jeffrey Epstein? Number
one. Number two, there's one there's one
email that she sent him saying
John Brennan, the CIA director, gave me
the CIA's highest honor today. Pretty
cool, huh? Or pretty great, huh? And
then she tries repeatedly to set up a
lunch between Jeffrey Epstein and John
Brennan. Why? To what end? And there's a
bigger question here, too, and that is
what kind of judgment did these people
exercise? We This woman is supposed to
be the president's personal
legal advisor, his personal attorney.
And and this is what she's doing.
And I I have a theory that I'm confident
about.
Why would she be so close to John
Brennan of all people?
Because every Tuesday morning at 7:00,
John Brennan
chaired the kill list meeting.
And we know that the kill list committee
was chock-full of attorneys,
White House, NSC, CIA, DOJ, just to make
sure that yeah, you can legally go out
and just kill these people this week,
and then we'll meet up again on Tuesday
and come up with another list of people
to kill. She was on the kill list
committee. I'm confident of it.
So, she's either murdering people or
she's chit-chatting with Jeffrey
Epstein. Again, what kind of judgment do
these people have? And then where did
she go? She became the general counsel
at Goldman Sachs.
>> That's right.
>> At least they had the presence of mind
to say, "You got to go.
>> They I will say this, they should have
done that a few years ago.
>> ago when it was when it was first
released that she was in touch with
Jeffrey Epstein. You're absolutely
right.
>> That's right. And like, you know,
there's just some there there's
revelations of people that had
stronger relationships to the point that
you know they were personally in his
life.
>> [snorts]
>> I want to come back to Rummler in a
minute cuz that's a big story, but like
Lawrence Krauss, I've said this a
million times, sat in that chair
2 years ago. Got connected to him
through someone else that was on the
podcast. He's a physicist. And then when
he was coming in here, we knew he had
known Jeffrey Epstein. I asked him about
it on the podcast. He was a nice enough
guy.
He's got 7,500
emails with Jeffrey Epstein. So like I'd
love to be like, you know, and and
usually like I have a policy of not
really talking against like people
who've been in here and stuff like that.
It's just like a part of the job. Let
other people do that, but
journalistically like you have to do
this. And I I'm not planning on reaching
out to Lawrence to ask him about this or
whatever, but
when you are coordinating with someone
that much over all these years and we
found out he was trying to get Jeffrey
Epstein on the Joe Rogan Experience in
2017,
>> You've got to be kidding me.
>> you know, bro. At that point you know.
And he said in the past, he was quoted
as saying like, you know, well, I only
ever saw Jeffrey around young women who
were 21 or 22, so I assumed that I
believed him, took him at his word when
he said he wasn't a part
>> that's exactly what Peter Mandelson said
until the picture was released of him in
his underwear with a 16-year-old not
realizing that he was being
photographed.
>> That's right. And it's got it's it's got
to be said like when you see there's
other people that are in the emails
where I don't really see anything and
it's only a couple emails and they don't
really seem to like know him well. I'm
like,
all right. It's weird, but all right.
But to bring it back to Cathy now,
11,500,
very interesting that you put two and
two together with the kill list, which
leads to my question. And again, some of
this has to be theorizing. John and I
Sure. We weren't [__] there, so we
don't know.
But do you think that Cathy, before we
get to the origins of Jeffrey Epstein
and go through all that, do you think it
was that Cathy as a rising star attorney
becoming kind of like fixer, especially
once she got into the Obama orbit when
he gets into office. Do you think
someone like that was just very clearly
a target for Jeffrey and he then
actually possibly befriended her and
then because of the connections he had,
she trusted him and with information
related to things like, I don't know,
perhaps a kill list?
>> I think that's likely. Because if you're
hearing from people like Alan
Dershowitz, "What a great guy Jeffrey
Epstein is, right?"
>> [laughter]
>> And you know, I know that's your best
friend. Yeah.
>> You love him.
>> Yeah, we Yeah, we really love each
other.
Um
Again, what kind of judgment do these
people have?
If you're like the most important
constitutional attorney in the world,
then maybe you should keep your pants on
>> Probably.
>> in the presence of a 16-year-old girl.
>> Yeah.
>> Your defense that that you're you kept
your underwear on, that's not a defense.
It's not a defense.
>> [snorts]
>> You know, I was on the Piers Morgan show
with him,
I don't know, 6, 8 months ago.
And Piers called it smackdown
afterwards.
Because
I think I rattled him. I rattled
Dershowitz. He He said the most
ridiculous thing.
I said that I was confident that Epstein
was a was a Mossad access agent. And I
believe that I've been proven correct. I
believe
that I underestimated his contact with
intelligence services. We could talk
about that all you want. Yeah.
Um but I I'm
positive that he was an Israeli agent of
some sort. And Dershowitz just jumped
all over me. And then he shouted See,
this is what he does, he interrupts to
try to knock you off off balance. But he
shouted the most ridiculous thing and I
laughed at him. He said that he was
Epstein's attorney. And if Epstein was a
spy for the Mossad, he could have gone
to the White House and he could have
gotten him a lighter sentence. And it's
like, "I would have hung him from a
tree.
>> [laughter]
>> No, John.
>> Oh, hung him from a
tree.
>> That's right. That's right.
>> Like, you think going to the White House
admitting that your client is spying for
a foreign power
>> Yeah.
>> on you.
>> That's right.
>> That's going to get him leniency.
>> I saw we can't play it because it
actually has like copyrighted music in
the background, but
I was just looking when right before you
got here that clip popped up in my feed
of him saying that. And it was actually
I don't know if you notice this cuz you
were just on Zoom like going back and
forth, but we can watch it afterwards
and see everything. You could tell as he
was getting through it once he had said
CIA or Mossad and then said, "I could
have gone straight to the white" He went
like
>> Uh-oh, crap.
>> Oh, whoops.
>> Cat's out of the bag.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah. And and you just see
Bassem Youssef like
He was good.
>> I want to ask you that.
>> You know what I mean? It was like,
"Whoa." But that's That's the thing,
John. And I've talked about this a bunch
recently. It's like
you're Greek-American, right? You're
born You're born here.
>> Born here.
>> Mhm. You're a dual citizen, right?
>> Yes.
>> But you're someone who served the
American government.
>> Well, I only became a dual citizen in 20
>> That's right.
>> 10.
>> That's right. Okay, so you're even
closer generationally. I'm like fourth
generation or something like that. I'm
half Italian, half Irish. No disrespect
to the Irish side. I love my Irish fans
out there.
You know, I never identify with the
culture. The food kind of sucks. I go
out of my way to not celebrate St.
Patrick's Day. It kind of is what it is.
It's not a part of my family cultural
history.
>> Right.
>> And so like if something happened with
Ireland tomorrow, I'd be like, "Ah,
that's really sad, but my life would go
on." On the other hand, the Italian side
>> Yeah.
>> that's my family culture on both sides.
That I have lived in the country. I have
family in the country. I love that
place. It's amazing. If tomorrow though,
as an American-born Italian-Irish
American, if the American [snorts]
government came to me and said, "Listen,
Jules,
some [__] went down last night and it
turns out we are at war with Italy. Will
you Before the question comes out like
will you fight for us or them? I have on
my American fatigues, an AK-47, and I'm
taking the nearest plane, train, or
automobile to get the [__] over to Italy
and mow down whatever Mario and Luigi's
get in my way in the wrong uniform. I'm
going to hate it. I'm going to hate it,
but I'm going to do it.
>> Yes.
>> And there's a lot of people whose names
ended in a vowel in 1943
>> Mhm.
>> whose parents didn't even speak English
who did the same
>> exactly that.
>> And there are many American Jews who
would say the same thing about America.
>> Mhm.
>> I take [clears throat] issue. I It's not
about the race. I take issue with anyone
like an Alan Dershowitz who you know
goddamn well, American-born dude who's
made his whole life here. You know
goddamn well, if you ask him that
question, do you get a blank stare and
he changes the subject and you know what
the answer is.
>> Or even just accuse you of being an
anti-Semite.
>> That's right.
>> I couldn't agree with you more.
Mhm. I don't trust him. I don't like
him. Frankly, I don't know anybody that
trusts him.
He's just not
the kind of guy that instills trust.
>> Yeah, and the thing about him
that I have to give him
is that ever since the Epstein story
like first came out, he is one of the
only people if not maybe the only guy
like from that orbit who will get in
front of whatever camera is rolling to
discuss the case directly. I will give
him that. I will also give him that as a
attorney, he did represent the guy. He
has a job to do there.
>> Yeah.
>> Whether we like it or not.
>> But David Boies was on uh the other He
and I were both on uh Piers the other
day and he made an important point cuz
David Boies is one of the most important
criminal defense attorneys in America.
And he said that Dershowitz was more
than just his attorney. He was his
friend and that's fine. You can be
friends with with your clients even if
your clients are scumbags, but he was
Epstein's publicist.
>> Mhm.
>> And that's not fine.
>> He was?
>> For all intents and purposes, yeah.
>> Interesting.
>> Mhm.
Yeah.
Did Did you happen to see Les Wexner's
testimony?
>> I'm glad you brought that up, John.
>> Did you catch the hot mic moment?
>> If you say more than five words, I'm
going to [__] kill you.
>> [laughter]
>> Yes, I did catch that.
>> I loved it.
>> How about the [__] the real
>> Yeah, uh-huh. Yeah. Boy, Les Wexner
I I would have so many questions for Les
Wexner
there aren't enough hours in the day.
>> Right. What would What would be the
first thing you'd ask him?
>> What would possess you to hire
a seventh-grade substitute math teacher
who had never finished college to be tax
advisor when you are the richest man in
the state of Ohio? There wasn't one
person
in the entire United States of America
for you to hire to advise you on your
taxes
than a seventh-grade substitute math
teacher who didn't finish college unless
you were also having sex with him.
>> Oh, I didn't see that curveball coming
at the end. That kind of just hit me.
>> Which Which he has consistently denied.
>> He has You see his reaction that with
his face when they did bring that up in
a separate question, I might add.
They're like, "Did you ever First of
all, he's like leaning forward like this
whole time." And they're like,
"Did you ever Did you ever have sexual
relations with Jeffrey Epstein?" He's
like,
I was like, "I need a body language
expert on that one. I don't know."
>> And you know what he did, according to
Vanity Fair? As As soon as people
started asking that question
he ran out and got married.
The guy was, you know, well into
adulthood and had never been married.
And then as soon as people started
saying, "I wonder if if Wes Les Wexner's
gay."
He ran out and got married.
>> See, this is what's strange
about that in particular. Now, I can't
speak for Les Wexner at all, but on the
other side of the equation
because these files, to be clear, seem
to show it's girls, boys, children just
in general. Anything
went. But on the other side of the
equation, in all the testimony,
witnesses,
people who were around Jeffrey Epstein
coming forward, I have never heard
something where it involved a male,
period. It was always young women
or
little girls, right?
So, for him to be this would be a, you
know, a
a gay relationship or encounter like
that, and that
I mean, I guess it's totally possible. I
guess nothing's off the table, but it's
a that's always been like a little bit
of a red herring for me. Like, I wonder
if it's like Les is doing stuff with
people that Jeffrey's providing.
>> And that that could very well have been
as well. Mhm.
>> Mhm. So, you you asked that question,
though,
about why you'd hire a
>> Yeah.
>> Dalton math teacher.
>> Why? And you give him so much money that
he ends up with
>> and and power of attorney.
He ends up with the widest townhouse in
all of Manhattan.
>> You ever stood outside that place?
>> I went once. Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's gigantic.
>> Yeah.
>> I give the demented tour of New York
City to people coming in town. We go
there.
>> That would be fun.
>> We stand there, but
>> Yeah.
>> it's a big place.
>> Yeah, it is.
>> You ever see look at the Google Maps and
see how far it goes back?
>> No.
No, I'll do that.
>> is like half the size.
>> Wow.
>> It's nuts. We'll get to Letney, by the
way.
>> Wow.
>> But this was an answer related to the
first half of your question, John. So,
let's let this play right here, Deef.
Why Les Wexner hired Jeffrey Epstein.
>> He had done personal
work for the Rothschild family in
France.
Well, specifically, I talked to Elie de
Rothschild and said mention that
earlier.
Uh
so,
he he represented their whole family. He
said there'd been a whole bunch of
people that
many most of them I never would have met
but in New LA
he would say like I'm I'm providing
financial advice to the founders of
Google.
I'm financial providing financial advice
to Jeff Bezos.
>> To be clear that was that was later.
>> question. Okay.
>> That was later when he did that that
wasn't from that answer right there but
it seemed to me when you see the foot
there's a
>> full 4 minute version of that as well
that what Wexner was saying whether it's
true or not is certainly a question but
what he was saying is that he was really
hitting at the point that like because
he personally talked to some of the
members of the Rothschild family and
they confirmed at the time this
allegedly being
in the mid to late 80s something like
that.
>> Right. Right.
>> That they were in fact working with
Jeffrey on whatever basis they were he
decided to do it.
>> bona fides. Yeah?
>> Yeah.
So
first of all do you believe that or do
you think there's more there?
>> Oh there's got to be more there. So far
in this entire story nothing has been as
it seemed. Nothing. There's there's been
more
behind all of it behind every
revelation.
And if only half of it's been released
and we're flipping out over what we've
seen so far
what's the other half include? You know?
And why wasn't it released? Is it even
worse than what we've seen? Is it just a
continuation of what we've seen?
I will say that there are a lot of very
important people out there who have
questions that need to be answered. I
hate that the statute of limitations is
a problem here. I hate that very much.
>> a problem specifically?
>> A problem in that
this stuff can't be prosecuted.
>> Which stuff?
>> Like child sex crimes.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
There aren't going to be any charges
against anybody. There going to be civil
suits
but nobody's going to be charged with a
crime. If you look at even in the UK the
UK's been very straightforward about all
this. They have Mandelson now and former
Prince Andrew. Andrew was charged with
um
with passing a document to Epstein that
had to do with British business and
trade negotiations.
>> Aliumama
>> Yeah. The Aliumama deal, that's exactly
right. And then Mandelson is rumored to
have given him something from the
Defense Ministry which could be a
violation of the state the official
secrets act.
Uh but none of this stuff has to do with
sex.
>> We'll come back to the Aliumama deal cuz
that has to do with like the origins
here. I just there is so much on the
bone that like it's so hard to stay on
one thing. So I apologize to people if
we jump around a lot, but like John
knows everything about this case. So
that'll happen a little bit. But
let's stay with Wexner for a minute.
So you'd ask him about the source of
wealth.
Then they have a relationship for at
least 20 years. He claims that he cut
him off in 2007. I don't know that I
believe that.
>> Right.
>> What else would you ask him?
What would be the burning or to quote
Howard Lutnick, the cutting question?
>> Yeah.
I mean, I would ask questions that I
know he wouldn't answer truthfully or
honestly. Like I would want run downs of
every time he went to that island.
There's there's a reason why
literally every room including the
bathrooms were wired for audio and
video.
>> Mhm.
>> Nobody does that.
>> He said he only went there once on his
boat with his family on the record.
>> Right.
I
I hope that's true. I don't believe him.
>> I agree.
>> Not if you've been a not just a friend,
but
but a a close friend, a best friend for
more than two decades. You went to the
guy's house one time? Come on.
>> It's like Dave was saying with Howard
Lutnick's answer at Congress where he's
like, "I went to the island. It was only
for an hour and I left with my wife, my
children, and our nannies."
>> Yeah. Cuz people fly all the way to the
Caribbean for 1 hour.
>> He's like he couldn't say Dave's like
you couldn't say you were there for the
afternoon. Exactly. I mean it's a
[__] island.
>> Exactly.
>> And that was after Ludnic denied that
they were close friends.
Mhm.
>> That [__] that one.
>> Look at Sarah Ferguson. Now she's in a
whole heap of trouble.
>> That's Prince Andrew's ex-wife.
>> Mhm.
>> Well, we knew for a long time that
Jeffrey was like floating her money cuz
they were in debt up to their eyeballs,
right?
>> I have a good friend who represented her
as as one of her attorneys and he said
she was always broke.
Always broke.
I don't know where the money went. How
can you be a member of the British royal
family and be broke? I have no idea.
>> That whole thing's sketchy.
>> Mhm.
>> I mean specifically targeting that, too.
>> And then after he's convicted
in 2007
and she says publicly that she's cut him
off. Then she emails him, "I'm so sorry,
Jeffrey. I love you. You're the big
brother I never had." And then she takes
her daughters down there to visit him.
And then lies about it.
Like what kind of hold did he have on
people? I don't understand this.
>> Do you think
I ha- I don't think this for a second,
but I have to ask this just so you can
at least respond.
Do you think some of these people
might have actually believed him at his
word that he's like, "Yeah, I
accidentally ordered a 17-year-old. I
thought I thought she was 21." Do you
think it's even possible that they would
have believed
>> I think it's possible that they
wanted to believe it and then allowed
themselves to believe it.
>> Yeah.
>> Deep down, no. Unless you're deaf, dumb,
and blind.
>> Yep.
>> Uh I can't imagine. No. Plus, you know,
it's not like people don't talk.
I mean, even Trump said back in the day
Jeffrey likes them young, too young for
my taste.
>> Yeah.
>> Mhm.
>> A lot of people said there's there's
even emails. I'm trying to remember
who it was with. Maybe it was actually
with Mandelson, but don't quote me on
that where they're going back and forth
and Jeffrey says
take a picture of of you and and send me
a picture of you and the little girl or
something like that." And the guy goes
like, "Haha, yeah, sure."
Ay yay yay. I I interviewed a member of
the British Parliament a couple days ago
for my my own podcast and um
and he said, "This is enough to bring
down the British government." Yeah.
Yeah. Like judgment. What kind of
judgment do you people have? And
look, Mandelson has always been
a scumbag, right? Everybody knew he was
a crook. He had been credibly accused
of, you know, embezzlement and
extortion. He's he's just a crook.
They're out there in politics.
And so when word surfaced that he was
close to Jeffrey Epstein and, you know,
he had already had to be removed as
business minister and from a another
couple of uh
senior positions in the in the British
Labour Party,
he swore to Keir Starmer, the now the
Prime Minister of the UK, he swore to
him that he barely knew Epstein. They
had met once or twice. There was nothing
to these rumors.
And then
the emails are released, including the
photo of him with a 16-year-old girl
standing in his underwear. They're both
looking at a laptop, so it's clear he
does not realize he's being
photographed.
And um
and then he had to admit that, "Okay,
all right, you caught me."
So,
he's resigned from the House of Lords.
He's been thrown out of the Labour
Party.
But people aren't just angry at
Mandelson.
And also he was recalled as the British
Ambassador to the United States. He's no
longer the ambassador. They're not angry
just at Mandelson. They're angry at the
Prime Minister because what kind of
judgment do you have
when everybody in the country knew this
guy was a scumbag, but because he looked
you in the eye and he smiled at you
and said, "Oh, no, no, Prime Minister,
it's not true. None of it's true.
And then your reaction is, "Okay, I'm
going to make you ambassador to the
United States of America."
What goes through their minds?
So this Kier Starmer may not last as
long as Liz Truss's head of cabbage.
This is This is bad.
>> [laughter]
>> I can already see the meme on that one.
Yeah, so you're also tying into directly
what Ro Khanna said. As well. And one
thing I like about Massie and Ro Khanna
is their delivery is the same with the
exception of I've never seen Massie get
worked up like he did at Pam Bondi. And
I
>> He rarely gets worked up.
>> That was happening to him. He genuinely
dislikes Pam Bondi.
>> Oh, yeah. She's a liar.
>> Mhm.
>> But
Ro Khanna will just like these two guys,
Massie and Ro Khanna, will just like
deliver this line about the Epstein
files. It's like, "Wait, I'm sorry. What
the [__] did you just say?" And it's
like, "Yeah, so uh we found this and
there it is. All right, have a good
one." They walk out. So Ro Khanna comes
out maybe like two, three weeks ago and
he had just walked out of the DOJ where
they he got to see some of the stuff
that they haven't released. And he was
like, "Yeah, so the files show that this
poses an existential risk for the entire
monarchy system in the UK and then
therefore across Europe cuz they're all
[__] related."
>> Yes. Literally.
>> Which, you know, John, I obviously we
kind of fought a war about that here
like 250 years ago. I'm not a huge fan
of monarchies. I wouldn't shed a tear.
But
>> a laughing emoji every time the Crown
Prince of Greece posts something on
Facebook.
>> I like that. Yeah.
>> Crown Prince of Greece, you're not even
Greek. You're Danish.
How dare you?
>> Shut up, malaka.
Get out of here. I like that. You got to
I'll retweet that when you do it. Let me
know when you do it.
>> But it's like the other problem with
this and maybe I'm like overthinking
this a little bit, but these systems are
so entrenched Yes. where
from a
backdoor economics perspective, whether
it be real estate holdings, financial
holdings, funnels of money, things like
that.
If it all came down at once,
>> Oh, boy.
>> crash the whole system.
>> Yes.
>> That's real?
>> I think it's real.
>> Yeah.
>> Um I was watching BBC this morning, as a
matter of fact, and they said, "As
recently as 3 years ago, 80% of the
British people support the monarchy.
Today, 50% of the British people support
the monarchy." Yeah. This is They're at
a tipping point.
And if the Brits go,
everybody else is going to go, too. Look
at Norway. Whoever even heard of the
Norwegian royal family? But now you got
ties to Epstein. You got the crown
prince's or crown princess's son talking
to women. Now he's got to go on trial.
What kind of people are these?
Like, is it really worth it
to to prop up these phonies as your as
your monarchs?
No, I don't think so.
>> it's That's not the question here.
That's not the question. It's like
like
if I were just responding with my anger,
I'd want the entire system. We're not
just talking monarchies. Let's just
[__] get a reset button. Right? But
[snorts] I also know
how much that would affect all of us if
it all happened all at once.
And so, that's the strange dance in
trying to go through this case. How do
you find a way to go in with the raid,
right, and hit all the cockroaches,
>> Right.
>> but not, you know, accidentally spray it
in grandma's mouth at the same time.
>> and and this is where you run into that
problem of statutes of limitations
again.
Because it would be far easier if you
could just prosecute these people. And
and show the people of every one of
these countries involved that it doesn't
matter how famous you are or how
important you are, we're all equal under
the law. And that's just not going to be
the case here.
All these famous rich people, they're
all going to get get with it.
It's sick.
>> You don't think anyone in the US will go
to prison for this?
>> I don't. You know, I was talking to a
constitutional attorney about this. And
he said the only way that this
that a prosecution could go forward is
if the Justice Department could
successfully argue
that
the cover-up of the original crime
continued and constituted a conspiracy.
So, you couldn't be
you couldn't be prosecuted necessarily
for the crime itself. You would be
prosecuted for conspiracy to commit the
crime.
But he said even that is a stretch.
>> What about with statutes of limitations
though? What about all the stuff we're
seeing like in this latest tranche where
these things are occurring but a lot of
it between 2011 and 2019.
I would think there's not a if if if you
were
doing cannibal acts on kids in 2015,
like we would be able to prosecute that.
>> some cases. On the on the sex cases, the
statute is 5 years.
>> Uh
>> And so we've missed it. Which, you know
what, may have been a part of the plan.
Why didn't Joe [__] Biden release all
this information?
>> you.
Every administration, I would argue
since Clinton, has covered this up. And
that's the thing.
>> Absolutely, yes.
>> Right? You have Trump in office right
now and there's a massive cover-up
happening and it should be called out.
We will call it out. It is what it is.
We'll talk about that more. But every
administration, R D, red and blue, has
had a chance to put this out. So, all
these Democrats who are suddenly just
jumping on the train here cuz they can,
right? And they can read a question
their intern gave them that's an easy
slam dunk because they covered this up.
It's like I have no energy for those
people either. This is this is a
systemic problem that has happened to
where you're just at a point now where
the Democrats are like, "Well, the
Clintons are so far past time and
they're so old and you know, like we can
now we can throw them under the bus.
They ain't like that no more."
>> Right.
>> Uh-huh.
But what about the victims then?
>> What they don't get
>> How how does that benefit the victims in
any way?
>> And why why you finally get to depose
Les Wexner, which
How about the fact he was listed as a
co-conspirator in the documents?
>> See, we never knew that.
>> And he's never been interviewed.
>> Never.
Like where was the FBI all these years?
And [snorts] another thing, too. And
this this goes back to the very basis of
this case.
>> [snorts]
>> Epstein got a sweetheart deal
in 2006, right?
And
the US attorney for the the
whatever it was, the southern district,
the central district of Florida,
whatever it was. I guess it was the
central district. Um
has said this is Acosta, who became
labor secretary in Trump's first term,
said that he was ordered to give this
this sweetheart deal. Okay, so where do
orders come? Who Who's the only person
in in the in the system there
who can order a US attorney to do
something? That's the attorney general.
Well, the attorney general was Alberto
Gonzales, who didn't brush his hair in
the morning without permission from the
president or the vice president, right?
He was like legendary for his
powerlessness and ill-suit- suiting for
the for the position.
So
was it Bush?
Was it Cheney?
Who was it that was close enough to
Epstein that he would want to swoop in
and save Epstein
by giving him the sweetheart deal?
Nobody's ever answered that question.
And Acosta
apparently genuinely doesn't know the
answer.
His order came down from the attorney
general.
>> I think I believe him on that.
>> too. I believe him.
>> Cuz he said he I was told he belonged to
intelligence.
>> Intelligence.
>> That's the line.
>> That was the word. He belonged to
intelligence.
>> Well, this gets into that super
government
>> Mhm.
>> kind of thing, cuz it's like
you say Bush and Cheney, which
makes a lot of sense to me, but not like
my whole world view is just like
>> Oh, yeah, that's ridiculous. You know, I
used to I used to just piss all over
people's analysis when they would start
talking about the Trilateral Commission
>> [laughter]
>> and Bilderberg and the Shangri-La
Conference. And then somebody
to whom I used to be very close
used to used to and
about whom
a court order exists saying I cannot
talk about her
um
in any public forum.
She went to one of those events.
She was invited because she rose up high
enough in the corporate structure that
she went.
And I I couldn't wait to hear. What was
it like?
And she said it's a lot of really rich,
really important people
talking about arms deals.
>> Arms deals.
>> It was all about arms deals. And she
said except for
except for Davos.
She went to Davos and she said
that's where they were all talking about
how to manage the global economy.
And I said, so
so all that shit's true?
That they're the ones that sort of set
the policy. And she said, yeah, I saw it
with my own eyes.
>> [snorts]
[laughter]
>> I
>> But I'm I'm not
>> you get me a pen and paper?
>> allowed to identify who that person is
nor will I.
>> It's on it's on the counter out there.
Usually I I've never needed that before,
but I I I may need that today after
after hearing that.
All right, so the Trilateral Commission
for people out there who are unfamiliar,
this is something that's been written
about a lot in the past and once again
it's something that's always written off
like, oh god, this is another conspiracy
>> theory.
>> Well
>> But it's
right?
It's all It's a real thing.
>> It is. They even have a website.
They have a website.
>> What's the website of the Trilateral
Commission?
>> And and Bilderberg, they list all the
people that attend. There's but by name,
all these people. And you'll recognize
80% of them.
>> Oh, man.
Well, I mean, I guess that's hiding in
plain sight. But it's something where I
I guess what I should say is the
connotation of it was where the
conspiracy theorists would be saying
something and people would be like, "No,
it's just this group. It's the It's
David Rockefeller." Like
>> I know, right?
>> Ferdinand Rothschild, you know, and
yeah, listen, they we put Clinton on it.
He was He was bored after he left
office.
You know, and then
you get Epstein in this this sit-down
with Steve Bannon. We we will talk about
him. But you get Epstein saying, "Yeah,
I was on the Trilateral Commission. And
here's how I got on." And he makes it
sound so simple.
>> Yeah. Right.
>> I'm like, "How do you even get there,
buddy? You're a kid from Coney Island."
>> Yeah, somebody taps you on the shoulder.
Next thing you know, you're getting an
email.
Dave, can you put the camera on John?
>> Yeah.
>> I I see what you're doing.
Mhm.
Son of a [__]
Really?
I knew it, but really?
>> Yeah. It was very
>> How's she good in there? God damn it.
>> very disappointing to me.
>> You can't talk about that by court
order?
>> No, sir.
>> Yeah.
I already didn't like her. Now I really
don't like her. But wow. Wow.
>> Yeah, this is the life I've given
myself.
>> And I'm just Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, this is the life I've given
myself.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay. So,
back to the Oh, wait, sweetheart deal
cuz we're talking about where that would
come from.
You know,
I'm trying to not let my brain run too
wild with now every possible answer is
right all over here. It's all like
absolutely the worst thing ever, but
clearly some of the answers are there.
So,
without getting to his origin story yet,
because that's again, we're going to do
that. But you talk about
at the Trilateral Commission, they are
going over arms deals and everything.
And now this is entering your world of
things that you have witnessed around
the world and how [__] works. What is it
about arms deals that would make it
the number one priority for the
quote-unquote Illuminati
>> Well, of the world.
>> Of the Pentagon's $1 trillion budget,
fully a third goes to weapons and
weapons systems. Right? That's just for
us.
>> Mhm.
>> So, couple that with what we're able to
sell to other countries whose leaders
are at these conferences. I mean, we're
talking about, you know, probably a
majority of the American economy year
after year after year.
That's how we employ Americans.
I read something recently
oh, the Washington Post, the New York
Times
that the Pentagon has assiduously placed
manufacturers
or I shouldn't say it placed
manufacturers. They have placed orders
with manufacturers
in literally every one of the 435
congressional districts.
So, literally every single member of
Congress has constituents who are
dependent on the defense economy.
On the defense budget.
And so,
there's no incentive for any member of
Congress to vote no on DOD.
>> And they're also paid by all those
companies.
>> Yeah, sure. I mean, it costs what? 5, 8,
10, 20 million dollars to run for
Congress? Every 2 years?
That money's got to come from somewhere.
So, it comes from Defense Department
packs.
>> They buy them off on the micro and then
it wins them the macro when you put the
numbers together. Yeah, Dief, what you
pull up here?
>> Just confirming it. Yeah.
>> All right. So, the Washington Post
reports that the Pentagon structurally
distributes manufacturing and
contracting across almost every
congressional district to secure broad
local political support, making budget
cuts difficult. The strategy embeds
defense spending into the local economy
with analysis showing that despite a
high concentration of funds among top
contractors, the broader supply chain is
deeply embedded in domestic districts.
>> And a friend of mine um has a little
kind of little mom-and-pop
manufacturing plant in Beaver County,
Pennsylvania.
>> AeroTech International?
>> No, no, no. It's a little
It's just a little place you've never
heard of.
>> Got it.
>> And he mentioned something to me one
time.
Oh, this is probably 5 years ago. He
mentioned that he is entirely dependent
on the Pentagon. And I was like, "The
Pentagon? I said, "For what?"
Oh, I can't tell you. He said, "It's
classified program." I said, "Seriously,
George?" Like, I thought he was making,
you know,
heels for shoes or something. I didn't
know what he was making. [laughter]
And then later on he told me like, "No,
it's this little widget that fits
inside, you know, the the motor for a,
you know, Patriot missile or something."
>> Nice.
>> And I was like, "In In Beaver County?"
And he's like, "Yeah."
And then when I saw that report in the
Washington Post, I was like, "Oh, of
course. It all makes sense."
>> Mhm.